Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory4 Mss.B.B61.inventory04
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents D
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 18; 1p
      - See FB to Rice, J., 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1903 n.d.; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 May; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 July 21
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p
    - LID -- to Gebhart, J.C., 1925 Mar. 30; 1p
      - LID -- to Michelson, N., 1930 Oct. 15; 1p
      - LID -- to Mills, 1934 May 11; 1p
    - LID -- from Wells, F.L., 1935 Aug. 6
      - LID -- from Lips, J.E., 1937 Dec. 1
    - LID -- to Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 23; 1p
  - Dublin, Mary (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 14; 1p
    - See FB to Columbia U. Fellowship Com, 1933 Mar. 3
  - Dubois, Constance Goddard (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 30
  - Dubois, W.E.B. (Box 23)
    - 1906 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1923 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1923 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 11; 1p
  - Dubos, Réne J. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Ducas, D. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Dudley, A.A. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 27; 1p
  - Duggan, Fred S. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Duggan, Laurence N? (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Duggan, Stephen P. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Auyg 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 July 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 1; 5p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 26; 1p
    - To Comm. Assis. Lesser Nationalities of USSR, 1928 Nov. 19; 2p.
      - co-signed: FB & Bogoras
    - To Moe, Henry Allen, 1928 Nov. 19; 2p.
      - co-signed: FB & Bogoras
    - To Leningrad Univ., 1928 Nov. 19; 2p.
      - co-signed: FB & Bogoras
    - From Harrison, Ross G., 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Capen, S.P., 1920 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Osborn, Henry F., 1920 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Pupin, M.I., 1920 May 3; 1p
    - From Sherwood, Geo. H., 1920 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Skillings, Everett, 1920 May 27; 3p
    - From Smith, Irwin, 1920 June 24; 1p
    - From Capen, S.P., 1920 Oct. 9; 1p
  - Duggar, B.M. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Duisburg, A. von (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Duke, Ephraim (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Dulles, S.H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p
  - Dunbar, Barrington (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 10; 1p
  - Duncan, John A. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 23; 2p
  - Dundas, Archie (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 14; 2p
  - Dundee Polar Fishing Co. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1884 Sep. 27; 1p
  - Dunham, L. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
  - Dunlap, K. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Dunn, Arthur W. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 26; 2p
  - Dunn, E.H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8
    - To Boas, 1913 June 10; 4p
  - Dunn, Gano (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 4; 1p
    - See Kennelly, A.E., 1936 Mar. 7
  - Dunn, James C. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 11; 1p
  - Dunn, J.J. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 29
  - Dunn, J.P. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7; 4p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7; 3p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 14; 2p
    - From Mooney, James, 1907 Sep. 25
    - From Mooney, James, 1907 Oct. 2
    - From Mooney, James, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Holmes, W.H., 1907 Oct. 21
    - From Holmes, W.H., 1907 Oct. 26
    - To Holmes, W.H., 1907 Oct. 24
  - Dunn, Prof. Leslie C. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8; 1p
      - Osborn, F. co-signed, 1937 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 24 & Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 13; 1p
      - see FB to LCD, 1934 June 20
    - To Boas, 1936 July 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 4; 1p
      - see Urey, H.C., 1938 Apr. 22
      - on margin of David, 1938 June 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 10; 2p
      - open letter with FB, 1941 Nov. 5
      - see Spitzer, Robt., 1942 May 20
      - see FB to NY Times, 1942 Oct. 25
      - see FB to NY Post, 1942 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 3p
    - From Breit, G. to LCD, 1935 Feb. 17
    - From David, 1938 June 21
    - From Fackenthal, F.D., 1933 Nov. 3
    - From Murrow, E.R., 1934 Oct. 5
    - From Rautenstrauch, W., 1938 Jan. 10
    - From Solmsen, F., 1934 June 24
    - From Van Doren, Mark, 1938 Jan. 12
    - To Bryan, R.W. from LCD, 1934 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Columbia U. Faculty fellowship commit., 1933 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Columbia U. Faculty fellowship commit., 1941 Jan. 7; 1p
    - Efron, D., 1938 Jan. 17; 1p
    - Fackenthal, F.D., 1933 Nov. 8; 1p
    - Gaston-Heye, H., 1940 Dec. 31; 1p
    - Hull, Cordell, 1937 Feb. 20; 1p
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1938 Jan. 12; 1p
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Dunn, R.W. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Dunn, T.A. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 25; 1p
  - Dunn, W.F. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 5; 1p
  - Dunn, Mrs. W.F. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 24; 2p
  - Dunne, B.B. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 17
  - Dunne, M.Walter (Box 23)
    - To Nicholas M. Butler, 1906 n.d.; 1p
  - Dunning, W.A. (Box 23)
    - From Butler, Nicholas M., 1917 Feb. 13
  - Dunsey, I.W. (Box 23)
    - To Petter, Rodolphe, 1940 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Durium Products Co. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p
  - Dunstan, R.T. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Durlach, Theresa M. (Mrs. Milton I.) (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p
      - (also see Heidgerd, May 4), 1931 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 31; ?
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 14; 1p
    - From Redefer, 1936 July 14
    - To Redefer, F., 1936 June 28; 2p
    - From Rosoff, P. to TMB, 11937 July 13
  - Durmashkin, Ralph L. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Dutcher, B.W. or B.N. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1915 June 11
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
  - Dutt, B.N. (Box 23)
    - To Hajar, S., 1914 June 8
  - Dutton, S.T. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30
  - Dwight, J. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 20
  - Dyar, Harrison G. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas (see margin FB-HGD), 1920 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 6
  - Dyett (Box 23)
    - See FB open letter, 1937 Dec. 31
  - Dyk, Walter (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas (see FB open let.), 1933 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 12; 1p
    - WD -- to Sapir, E., 1937 June 2; 1p
  - Dykema, P.W. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 17; 1p
  - Dyrenkowa, N. (Box 23)
    - see Winnikow, T., 1930 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1930 June 12; 3p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 8